My brother Nihal used to say.
Life plays games with everyone.
But a real player,
plays with life.
Fearlessly. Daringly.
And his mind is a little --
The stakes are higher this time.
The cops are on high alert.
250 for pole touch
500 for sliding.
1000 for the parapet.
And rooftop.
-How much?
-Twenty.
Twenty?
-Twenty what?
-Twenty thousand!
Because it's a dangerous stunt.
All go, no show!
Okay, deal.
But...who's up for it?
Who else?
I will.
Siddhu!
♪ One, two, three. ♪
♪ Move a little left,
move a little right.♪
♪ Watching my play,
everyone will be psyched. ♪
♪ Such is my nature,
madness knows no height. ♪
♪ My passion burns like fire,
be it day or night. ♪
♪ Never stop, never tire,
like a carefree cloud. ♪
♪ Zipping through the skies
all by myself. ♪
♪ I strike like thunder
out of nowhere. ♪
♪ Everyone accepts defeat
when they watch me play.♪
♪ There fun fight for another pay back.♪
♪ Win the phase and now gonna hold back.♪
♪ I play fearlessly and daringly. ♪
♪ And my mind is a little -- ♪
Crack. He is totally crack.
♪ Crakk. Crakk. Crakk. Crakk. Crakk. ♪
♪ Get out the way,
I am gonna wreck. ♪
♪ Crakk. Crakk. Crakk. Crakk. Crakk. ♪
Passengers,
please pay attention.
♪ Crakk. Crakk. Crakk. Crakk. Crakk. ♪
He is winning.
♪ Never stop, never tire,
like a carefree cloud. ♪
♪ Zipping through the skies
all by myself. ♪
♪ I strike like thunder
out of nowhere. ♪
♪ Everyone accepts defeat
when they watch me play."♪
Hey, move side.
Hello.
A mad man is on the roof-top
of the train.
Wait, I will go and check.
In which compartment is he?
♪ Crakk. Crakk. Crakk. Crakk. Crakk. ♪
Run. Cops.
v♪ I play without fear. Boldy. ♪
♪ And my mind is a little -- ♪
♪ Crakk. Crakk. Crakk. Crakk. Crakk. ♪
It will be done now.
-Do your job properly!
-I am doing it, Mr. Dixit.
Dixit!
The cops nearly arrested me today.
They should
lock you up forever.
If you keep this up,
all my pension money will be spent
in getting you out of jail.
I am your son.
You don't have any other choice.
-What did you say?
-Hey, Siddhu.
When is the next stunt?
Right now.
At home, with my father.
-Want to join me?
-Hello, uncle.
Hello, uncle.
He is a kid, uncle?
A kid?
I've grown old waiting for him
to grow up.
You have started again.
Youth is a feeling.
Don't blame me
if he doesn't feel that way.
Look at Dhoni.
At the age of 32,
he lifted the World Cup.
What did you do?
Do you want me to lift something?
There you go.
-Siddhu.
-You fool!
God made you a natural sportsman.
Had you played for the country,
you would have got a job, a medal.
And pension after retirement.
The outcome of the game you want to play
is death, son.
Nothing more.
And no one knows that
better than us.
People are dying out there anyway.
Except for a few games,
all one gets is a metal cup
and a couple of medals.
You do know who I'm talking about.
Brijesh Dixit!
My father.
He bagged three bronze medals
in the Commonwealth.
And now, he worries every day
for his son's salary and pension.
Stop it, Siddhu.
Sport is my passion.
I don't want my photo
in the newspaper,
but I want to see the sunset from
a skyscraper.
Honestly speaking, father.
I want money, that's all.
-Siddhu.
-Come on.
-I'll give you money.
-Listen.
-You want money, don't you?
-Listen to me.
-Don't interrupt.
-Please don't do this.
-Siddhu.
-You keep quiet.
Siddhu, what is going on?
Please don't pay attention. Please!
You want money, don't you?
Here's the money.
Pick it up.
Take it!
And go buy that dream house of yours!
Pick it up.
Can't touch it, can you?
Your brother also
went after this money.
Only the bag came back.
Since then,
none of us touched this bag.
Neither you nor me nor her.
Why?
Speak up, Siddhu.
Siddhu, where are you going?
Siddhu. Siddhu.
Siddhu!
♪ It's okay
if we couldn't be together for life. ♪
if I had to say goodbye. ♪
♪ It's okay
if we couldn't be together for life. ♪
if I had to say goodbye. ♪
♪ It's okay
if the journey has come to an end. ♪
if you never hear about me again. ♪
♪ It's okay. ♪
♪ Have no qualms, my friend. ♪
♪ Always keep that smile on your face. ♪
Are you okay, bro?
I am if you are there.
♪ Take care. ♪
♪ For my sake, take care. ♪
♪ It's okay
if we can't meet every evening. ♪
♪ It's okay if
you'll miss me every step. ♪
♪ It's okay. ♪
How do you always win?
-Duck, tuck, roll
-What?
Listen.
Duck down, tuck your shoulders.
And look straight.
Understood.
♪ Have no qualms, my friend. ♪
♪ Always keep that smile on your face. ♪
♪ Take care. ♪
♪ For my sake, take care. ♪
Stop on the side.
-I'll make sure,
-Sir.
-you two stay in jail forever.
-Unbelievable.
Do you want to take an exit from life?
Not exit, sir.
We want to enter.
Oh really?
Where?
Tell him.
Shrikant sir,
there are places
where people let go of themselves.
And there are places where
they redeem themselves.
Maidaan.
It's a world of extreme sports,
where players from all over the world
risk their lives to compete. Do you know?
The stakes are so high,
that even your calculator
will fall short of numbers.
My true love!
Bro, our true love.
Is this a playground or a superstar?
But how to get there?
It's simple, uncle.
Keep uploading such videos
on the internet.
They will watch and send an invite.
They will send an invite,
to both of us.
We'll enter the Maidaan,
conquer it,
and give everyone
a tough fight.
♪ Take care. ♪
♪ It's okay. ♪
No.
Yes.
The rat is here.
Hey, Philip.
How was your date last night?
-It was good.
-Good.
Let's play.
Since when have you
been dating the police?
You see.
God doesn't need a reason to kill.
But I have one.
Only one.
Betrayal.
Your informer is dead.
You put him there.
You are responsible.
Sir, we all know these races,
these games,
this Maidaan is illegal.
These junkies
are no national threat.
Sir.
Dev.
This man is responsible for
smuggling something dangerous,
into our country.
Maidaan is just a cover.
I'll figure that out with the Interpol.
You stay out of it.
No more informers.
Understood?
Uncle.
Who are you selling balloons
in the sea at this late hour?
You.
I'm past the age
of playing with balloons.
Only the game has changed, son.
And the Maidaan.
Want to come?
I say count me in.
Whatever you say.
Take me along. Maidaan is what
I have dreamt about all my life.
Hop on.
Uncle.
♪ One, two, three. ♪
Starve them.
Sir,
I think we need to take permission
from the four founding members.
Jack!
Permission is taken
when you're not sure
what you are doing is right.
Now send out that invite
for the bid.
Sir.
Sir, Siddhu...
What did you think?
Got arrested again?
Not this time.
Two more boys died today
while doing gimmicks on top of the train.
Are you aware?
I'm out of words, uncle.
The afternoon local train
heading from Ghatkopar to Panvel
Go look someplace else.
witnessed two more deaths
of boys performing stunts.
The boys were of 16
and 18 years of age.
Both the boys belonged
to Ghatkopar's Gangawadi chawl.
I knew you would show up.
Are you alright?
I am if you are there.
Siddhu, why did you come to Maidaan?
Go back to mom and dad.
Look at me.
I came here as a living-breathing
human being.
And now, I am drifting
as your conscience.
I came here so that you don't have to drift.
If I win, you will attain salvation.
Don't preach your elder brother.
Go fulfil your dream.
Guys, come out.
Our dream.
Alright, guys.
Get in the trucks.
This side in here,
this side over here.
Let's go.
Move it.
Morris. Africa.
Siddhu. India.
Butter chicken.
Hello.
When the whole world
plays in light,
we play in shadows.
Let me tell you what is Maidaan.
Today,
I will tell you what Maidaan is.
Maidaan is a home.
From today it's your home.
Maidaan has only one ideology.
Which is freedom.
The freedom you have all been
searching for in your free countries.
But have been unsuccessful so far.
Because we all know
freedom comes at a price.
That's why,
I am giving you
a chance to earn it.
So that you can go back
to your free country
and buy it.
Welcome. Welcome. Welcome.
Welcome to the most-watched event
in the world!
Welcome to Maidaan!
As the saying goes,
"Everything is fair in love and war".
All is fair in love and war.
Maybe.
But not here.
Because there are rules.
The rules you follow
are the rules I follow.
And those are the rules of Maidaan.
We are your passport and your visa.
We make the law and the rules.
The system and the procedure.
Because at Maidaan,
your safety is our concern.
And beware,
Maidaan has many enemies.
It's my duty to keep them away
from you.
So you'll be allowed to go
on the other side of the gate.
But once you're on this side,
there will be no phones.
No one from the outside
can contact you.
And you cannot contact
anyone in the outside world.
Never take off the bracelets
given to you.
Where, how and what you are up to.
We will always know every detail.
We watch everything.
So please don't do anything stupid.
Three races.
800 million.
The player who wins the first race
will win 160 million.
240 million for winning
the second race,
and 400 million for the third race.
Any player who wins
all three races in a row,
will win 800 million.
This year,
the player who wins
maximum races
will be Maidaan's champion.
And he will get another chance.
To double his winnings.
The challenger race.
And you've to play with me.
And if he defeats me,
then money is one thing.
He will get fame
and respect,
which none of you must have
ever imagined.
But if he loses,
then his winnings
will become zero.
Zero.
And once again, players.
Welcome to Maidaan!
Number 24.
Number 15.
Number 21.
Number 32.
Mark,
what do you think?
Who can challenge death?
The one who is worthy,
will reveal himself.
They have just announced
their upcoming contestants.
I'll call you back.
Anyone interesting?
Yes. Number 10.
Siddharth Dixit.
He has a history of Maidaan.
What history?
His brother Nihal Dixit,
competed in the finals
four years ago against Dev
and died.
Alright, listen up.
One night of fun.
Now remember, guys.
It's rules before drools.
Meaning if you break the rules,
he'll break your neck.
What is your role here?
I handle the betting.
I am the bookie of Maidaan.
Junaida.
So what's my rate?
That depends on you.
Whether you are eliminated
or you dominate.
But make Mother India proud,
please.
Speaking of mother --
You must have a phone.
Good evening, gentlemen.
The most crucial element
of making a nuclear bomb.
Plutonium.
This is just a sample.
And it can belong to one of you.
The bid starts at 100 million.
Once the advance is received,
the main consignment will be delivered.
Mom.
Siddhu.
Where are you?
I can lie to you if I want.
But I won't.
I am in another country.
Same place where brother went.
Brother?
You didn't listen.
Siddhu.
I did, father.
To myself.
And yes.
I am sorry
for whatever happened the other day.
Another thing.
This time it won't be just the bag.
-I will come back too.
-He will get me killed.
Idiot!
Come on.
-I'm hanging up.
-Quickly.
Listen.
Push! Push! Push! Push!
What say we rate the competition?
Done.
Hailing from Ricky Ponting's hometown.
Australia.
You alright, mate.
Mate's gonna make him checkmate.
Look at him.
Russia. Expert in vodka and junk.
She will break him from the inside.
Yeah!
Thank you, guys.
I swear, my love.
He will gallop like an Arabian horse.
He will gallop so hard
that he will trounce everyone.
Marvelous.
Oh yes, he's hot.
Ni-Hao Ma.
Kung Pao Chicken Sao Pao.
The Chinese will definitely lose.
But if she makes up her mind,
she's tough to beat.
Watch. Tough.
She is tough, man.
It's my turn.
Who is she?
Who's next?
Come. You want to face me.
-Come.
-Alia.
-Come, let's go.
-She is the influencer of Maidaan.
Who is going to face me?
You?
God, it's hot.
Hey!
Alia. Alia. Alia. Alia.
Let's go.
India? Poland?
Where are you from?
For now,
I am beyond your reach.
I am in love with you, girl.
That's how an Indian is.
A slight distraction and
an accident occurs.
Hey, listen!
I like girls who are
beyond my reach.
You are perfect!
Leave it.
Stop trying.
You won't get it.
What?
Number.
You won't get my phone number.
It's all you boys think about.
From the moment I saw you,
my mind has become numb,
and my buddy down there is awake.
Excuse me?
Look.
I meant my mind up here
and my heart down there.
My heart is awake.
What did you think?
Whatever.
Anyway.
I'll see you at the race.
Bye.
I'll be the only one you see
at the races.
I promise.
Good luck, man.
-Happy to see you.
-You too.
Freaking sissy.
This year Maidaan begins
with an open playground.
Maidaan! Maidaan! Maidaan!
-Alright, let's go.
-Yes.
Let's do this.
So excited now.
Hey, guys. Look. Look.
Sissy. Look at sissy.
You want some.
Do you have peanuts?
Maidaan! Maidaan! Maidaan!
There he is.
Siddhu.
Maidaan! Maidaan! Maidaan!
Put my bet on fifteen.
-Who are you betting on?
-Siddhu!
-Number 10!
-Let's go.
Team India!
Maidaan! Maidaan! Maidaan!
Welcome to Maidaan!
Okay, let's make some money.
Thirty-two players chosen
from around the world,
and the number will keep
decreasing by half after each race.
For instance, 32 in the first race.
16 in the second.
And 8 in the third,
who will compete
in the final race.
Now the rules.
There are 16 flags on that truck.
The players who grab the flag,
will qualify for the next race.
But --
the top speed of this truck
is 160 km/hr.
And top speed of humans is 44 km/hr.
So...
go-karts.
The target of the players is
to climb on these go-karts.
And the go-kart's target
is the players themselves.
Because these go-karts
are remote-controlled.
The players must climb aboard
these go-karts,
and take manual control.
Once they have manual control,
they must climb atop the truck
as soon as possible.
Because each go-kart
has a built-in timer.
Some 30, some 60
and some 90.
To each his own luck.
And remember,
there are only 16 flags
and 32 players.
So play well.
Because if you play,
you win.
And if you win,
you play again.
-Yes, got it.
-The race has begun.
Three, two, one.
Go!
Let's go.
Give me my screens.
He's trying to get on.
I don't think
he's going to make it.
One down, sir.
I can't believe this crap.
Whoa.
Number 10 is in Superman mode.
Zero gravity.
Soaring through the air.
Oh, he has done it.
He has done it.
The thing with Maidaan is,
it's not just about skills,
it's also about luck.
Fantastic jump, bro!
Like a rocket!
Whoa!
-That's a brave move. Who's that guy?
-Number 10, sir.
We've a partnership between
the African and the Indian now.
How did I do it?
And we've got
a few disqualifications obviously.
Aunty, Siddhu's match is coming on.
Aunty, come.
Yes, aunty. Come.
Siddhu's match is coming on.
Aunty, come on.
Yes, yes. Yes.
Go, go!
Oh God, number 10 is out of the race.
It was a good beginning.
But it looks like
number 10 is out of the race.
Yes, Sid. Come on.
If this isn't madness, then what is?
Keep tracking number 10.
Jump.
He is crack.
You would have died
and gone to heaven. Come on.
Teamwork.
Interesting.
The timers on the go-karts
are running out.
Okay, that's one more go-kart
that has stopped.
Another go-kart shuts down.
I think he's on.
He's going to make it.
Yeah. We got a winner.
We got a winner.
Wow! That was unexpected.
Only three flags left
out of sixteen.
Come on.
Don't give the country a bad name.
Two flags
and seven contestants.
Let's see who makes it
to the finish.
Who grabs the last flag?
Number 10 or number 26!
Yeah!
♪ Crakk. Crakk. Crakk. Crakk. Crakk. ♪
And these sixteen...
Final sixteen on the truck
going straight to the next race.
Yes. Siddhu.
The race was won by an Arab,
but it's the Indian who has won our hearts.
Number 10,
India aka Crakk.
This guy Siddhart
is catching a lot of eyes.
It's time to meet him.
You all made it here.
Congratulations.
You are anything but ordinary.
So don't expect an ordinary death.
Tomorrow if someone dies like them,
then the amount you have won so far,
will be given to your family.
We won't mourn,
for those who died today.
Rather we will celebrate
their life
and their death.
We celebrated them
when they were alive.
And we will celebrate them in death.
So no grieving.
No feeling bad.
They are your heroes.
Seek their blessings.
And all the best for race 2.
How are you?
Oh, my God!
Welcome to the party
after the first race.
How have you been, sweetie?
Hey!
How have you been? Good?
Alright.
Sid. Oh, my God. You killed it.
Where were you?
I wanted to tell you that...
Leave it.
Sympathy for others and aloofness for me.
If you were one of them,
why did you show so much of attitude?
Hello.
Don't be so judgmental.
They are escorts.
I'm a social media influencer.
Different professions.
Then stay away.
If staying away from them
will change your perspective about me,
then you need to change
your perspective, not me, my friend.
Listen.
I am from Mumbai.
I am used to seeing pollution before the sky.
And everything is going wrong today.
Please. Forgive me today.
You know what,
let's watch each other
without any filters tonight.
♪ No one has ever loved me. ♪
♪ Like you did. ♪
♪ You made my life difficult. ♪
♪ No one has ever loved me. ♪
♪ Like you did. ♪
♪ You made my life difficult. ♪
♪ It's not my fault. ♪
♪ Floored by your first sight,"
"I dedicated my heart to you. ♪
♪ You made my life difficult. ♪
Hey, no looking back.
Red is my favourite too.
I see.
Tell me three red things you like.
My favourite is "Lalbaugcha Raja".
Yes.
The spicy red mashed veggie dish
of Chowpatty Beach.
Okay. And?
And the way my mom slaps me.
She really makes my cheeks red.
I wish I had a mom
who would slap me.
How about my mom?
Really?
♪ I didn't realise how you became mine. ♪
♪ I didn't set my heart on you,
yet my heart is yours now. ♪
♪ God created love. ♪
♪ He brought us together. ♪
♪ He created events, ♪
♪ that brought you to me. ♪
♪ It's not my fault. ♪
♪ Floored by your first sight, ♪
♪ I dedicated my heart to you. ♪
♪ You made my life difficult. ♪
"It's not my fault..."
Good God.
Two lotteries in the same night.
Jackpot.
This time you're the lucky guy.
Wow. Hindi.
I speak thirteen languages.
Inspector Patricia Novak.
Madam, I only kissed her,
with her permission.
Cops in India don't let us
enjoy Valentine's Day.
And out here, it's you.
What is the problem?
The problem is not you,
it's Dev.
I've heard he's bringing
a consignment,
which can be a threat to Poland.
I need your help to catch him.
Madam. I am a sportsman,
-not Agent Vinod.
-Siddharth.
You think I am requesting you.
She's brought the cavalry.
You don't have a passport,
and you are in our country.
I can keep you in jail for life.
And when faced with trouble,
will Dev save you or himself?
What do I have to do?
You have to plant this chip on Dev.
So we can hear his conversations.
"Move a little left,
move a little right."
"Watching my play,
everyone will be psyched."
Why did you hit me?
Where is Dev?
I'll talk to him.
Explain him everything.
You want to fight?
Get him. Come on.
Sid, what happened?
What the bloody...
He hit me first.
Enough.
That cop was tracking me.
I did nothing.
Take a break.
She was blabbering something
about smuggler, Maidaan.
She cited your name.
Said I am here without a passport.
And this...
She told me to stick this,
on you!
It's a tracking device.
Sid. Sid. Sid.
You have a history with Maidaan.
Now listen.
Mic check.
-One, two, police.
-What's happening?
The chip is active.
I know you are Nihal's brother.
I didn't bring you here randomly.
Listen.
Inside Maidaan I am the law.
You tell me what you want.
I snatched the prey from
the python's mouth for the lion.
Now you are asking me what I want.
Good.
You understand the laws of the jungle.
I know, bro.
-The lion is the only king of the jungle.
-That's it.
Damn it!
Shit.
Hope I wasn't too gentle with you.
Freeze. Police!
Everybody let's go.
-Get back in. Get back in.
-Get the stuff out.
-Drop your weapons.
-Stop the van.
-Go. Go.
Everybody stop that van.
Shoot back.
Shit!
-Shit!
-Cover me. Cover me.
Go. Get it up. Get it up.
Go, go, go.
Don't move.
They say we've brought something
to their country
that we shouldn't have.
Did we, Mark?
Sir, Zack is arrested.
The consignment is safe,
but he has the password.
He doesn't have the password.
He is the password.
Race 2 is a go.
Taking you live through it all.
Ready to steal your hearts.
Fans are excited
and so are we.
It's a full house,
as you can see.
-Sea of players out there,
-Fans can't wait
-for the race to start.
-but Siddhu's on a roll.
Get forensics in.
I want every inch
of that chopper scanned.
How did we know about this?
I gave Siddharth two chips.
One he exposed,
and the other he planted on Zack.
He didn't betray us after all.
Today, Maidaan is in danger.
Thanks to Dev.
As long as I am alive,
there will be no threat to Maidaan.
Sir, if the police find out
what the consignment is,
it's all over.
We just got the forensic report
of the chopper.
You have to see this.
A-grade plutonium?
Then cancel today's race
for the sake of Maidaan.
Get off me.
Take it off.
A-grade plutonium radiation
was found in the chopper.
What's your plan?
I don't know.
And even if I did,
why the hell should I tell you?
I know how you freaking caught me.
It was that rascal, right?
That Indian.
He snitched.
We're going to kill him,
just like his brother!
His brother?
How did his brother die?
What?
Oh, my God! No, no, no.
Hey, Patricia madam.
Siddharth.
Yes, Siddharth.
Saying yes is what got me
in trouble.
Dev knows I led you to Zack.
-Get me out of here right now.
-Hold on. Hold on. Be patient.
You're telling me to be patient.
My life is in danger, madam.
There is a threat to my life.
Don't you get it?
Get me out of here.
-Do what you have to.
-Okay. Okay. Okay.
I'm sending you
a location on this number.
Be there.
My man will come and see you.
Done.
Let's play.
Dude, do you know how to get to India?
Go straight.
Sid. Sid.
You okay?
I'm making arrangements
for your departure.
Until then, you are safe.
Madam, no one here is safe.
You are not safe either.
Get out.
Honestly, get out of here.
What?
What the...
-Go, go, go.
-Take cover.
Don't shoot. Don't shoot.
Team Patricia, understand?
Go?
What the...
Team Maidaan.
Right?
Try to understand.
I am on your side.
Try to understand,
what I am saying.
-Put the detonator down,
-Easy, boy.
or I will shoot you.
Hold on. Listen.
♪ Crakk. Crakk. Crakk. Crakk. Crakk. ♪
Hello, Password. Shall we go?
Shit.
Guys, this whole place
is rigged to blow.
Whoa.
Stop or I will blow this place up.
You aren't the only nutcases around here.
I live for my country.
-And I will die for it.
-Goodness gracious. What is she doing?
Nobody move.
Sid, what are you doing?
-Sid. Sid, what are you doing?
-What are you doing, madam?
I will blow it.
Guns down.
-You blue shirt, down.
-Siddharth.
Down.
Siddharth.
Not you guys, bro.
Loyalty. Maidaan. Team.
-Siddharth.
-Understand?
What Siddharth?
Enough with Siddharth.
You tell me to stick a chip
or go after Zack.
I am not some delivery boy, madam.
I am a sportsman.
And bro respects sportsmen.
He got me here through a ship.
Gave me five-star accommodation
in his castle.
This watch...
Even gave us this watch.
So we don't go missing.
He is not Dev.
He's God. God.
It's a little dramatic,
but I mean every word.
Nihal.
I am Siddharth.
Nihal what?
What Nihal?
He didn't die in the race.
Your "God" killed him.
Him.
What is she saying?
I killed his brother?
And gave him a chance
to be the champion in Maidaan?
-Interesting.
-Leave all that.
Yes or no?
Did you have a problem
with my brother?
Your brother died in a sport.
You liar! He is lying.
Turning a murder into an accident
and vice-versa,
who would know it better than them.
Zack told me that they killed
your brother.
Stop messing with my brain.
I am telling you I will press it.
And you.
Are you threatening me, boy?
Out with the truth
or I will take everyone with me.
I am really getting pissed off now.
I will count till five.
And if you don't hand me the detonator,
I will come over there
and press it myself. Got that?
One.
Save the other four,
for your funeral.
No, Siddharth.
-No, No.
-No.
Leave me. I will kill you.
Cover him.
I will kill you, you rat.
Let me go.
Come on.
Move. Come on.
Take him.
-Let me go.
-Come on. Move.
Let me go.
Take him now. Go.
Are you okay?
I am if...
No, no.
Now I am not!
Welcome to the final race
of Maidaan.
In the final race,
the contenders are...
Nihal.
And Dev!
It was quoted in 1980,
that in the future,
all kinds of travel
will be done in the air.
And not on the ground.
And in Maidaan,
that future has arrived.
These bikes will be dropped
from an altitude of 40,000 feet.
Until the players don't get
on these bikes floating in the air,
they cannot open their parachutes.
The target of the race
is to obtain the flag,
which is placed in the middle
of the city.
Whoever lifts the flag first,
will be the winner of this race.
So, guys,
let's play.
♪ Crakk. Crakk. Crakk. Crakk. Crakk. ♪
Come on.
Bro.
Hey.
Can I have my phone back?
Lost you in Maidaan
Hand over your gun and badge.
No questions asked.
You are suspended.
You sided with the guys
who killed my brother
and you backstabbed me.
You clicked my picture
and gave it to them.
I thought you are my girlfriend.
-I didn't know.
- I was in love with you.
But you showed your class.
Let me explain.
Shut up.
Put the plutonium delivery on hold.
The cops are watching us.
We cannot take a chance.
But good.
Tell the buyers we deliver
on the final day of the race.
Stop it.
What?
Run over me.
-Run over me.
-What is wrong with you?
I will call the police.
-Move out of here.
-You want to die?
-Run over me.
-Let's go from here.
What are you doing?
Stop fooling around, understood?
I will cause a riot here.
They separated us. These...
Hey!
What about our mom?
Siddhu.
You were phenomenal
when you were playing Maidaan.
Fantastic.
What if something happens to you
if you get in this mess?
Ever thought about that?
Did you think?
If you die,
then what about me?
Did you?
So you will make the same mistake
that I did.
Great.
But don't forget,
you are mom and dad's last hope.
Don't take that away from them.
This is my life.
That was your life, this is mine...
Quiet!
My life?
What my life?
Who gave you this life?
They did.
Did they do a favour?
Then you do them a favour.
Like you did?
By stopping me from entering Maidaan.
Tell me.
You stopped me, didn't you?
What were you trying to hide?
Tell me.
I asked everyone...who do I ask?
Where do I go?
Tell me. Why?
Who do I ask, bro?
Tell me what these guys did.
Brother!
JD on the rocks, please.
JD on the rocks.
I'll be right back.
Yeah.
Celebrating my destruction, aren't you?
Get out of here.
I've no interest in going to prison.
But I'm in this mess because of you.
Got that?
Tell me about my brother.
Because if he died in the game,
then he's accepted that
and so have I.
Not by treachery.
You betrayed me,
and I lost my job.
You gave Zack to Dev,
who has the password
for the plutonium.
Do you know what that is?
A chemical that is used
to make nuclear bombs.
I just want to know the truth
about my brother, understood.
Alright.
You want to know the truth
about your brother,
and I want the plutonium's location.
And only one man can tell us that.
Mark.
But for that, you will have
to go back to Maidaan.
-Looks like the audience can't hold on.
-Did you see that?
-The crowd is going crazy for Dev.
-They are pumped.
Hundred bitcoins on number 10.
Number 15.
Put my bet on number 15.
Maidaan! Maidaan! Maidaan!
Welcome to the eliminations.
Only one step away
from the final race.
Today, the hunters are going
to be hunted.
So, let's meet the most faithful animal
on the planet.
Today, they will set
an example of disloyalty.
Two hundred hungry dogs
and the contestants on rollerblades.
In this race,
you will all get a partner.
A teammate
who will not slow you down.
They are all trained professionals.
You will be tied to your partner,
and the dogs were made to sniff
the clothes of your partner.
So obviously, their target
will be your partner.
The first way to lose
is if you break these shackles,
and try to get rid of your partner.
Second, if you go beyond
these compound walls.
And third...
Any guesses?
If you become the dog's prey.
There is only one way
to win this race.
There are seven red flags
in this castle.
When you obtain the flag,
a protective cage will envelop you.
And you will qualify
for the third race.
But remember, only qualify.
To win this race,
you must find the white flag.
The player who finds that
will be the winner of the race.
And he will also get
the winning amount.
And now, for some breaking news.
One of the sixteen contestants
is not a part of Maidaan.
And that is contestant number 10.
-Can you believe this? - What?
- What is this?
What could have happened?
I don't know, aunty.
Sir, more than half the bets
were on number 10 Siddharth.
Let the race begin.
-Siddhu!
Siddhu! Siddhu!
Here comes the hero.
Time for some action.
Number 10.
Brilliant.
The crowd's favourite number 10,
is back in the race.
Ready for the ride.
Siddhu! Siddhu!
I will play.
Nihal was a sportsman
and he knew,
the difference between victory
and defeat was only one second.
He knew that when he came here.
And he died while playing.
And listen to another thing
I came here to compete in Maidaan,
and not to get in any trouble.
I will win Maidaan.
Everything else can go to hell.
But,
do I want it?
That is the question.
When I win and you win the jackpot,
shall I give the answer after that?
The money I win from you,
I'll donate it for your
neighbourhood games.
You can go play there.
That is your class.
Not in Maidaan.
Keeping in mind,
the wishes and interest of our fans
and spectators from around the world,
the founding members of Maidaan
have decided that,
Number 10 will be allowed to participate.
No way.
-He's back.
-Siddhu is back.
Yeah.
Number 10.
Siddhu! Siddhu!
Okay.
They want you to play.
But there is a problem.
You need a partner in this game
which you don't have.
And rules are rules!
For you, for me.
For everyone.
Everyone, right?
Is anyone willing
to team up with this traitor?
Me!
How sweet!
One wants to play for her love
and the other for his brother.
I will play.
And win it.
Restart the countdown.
The show is about to start
Five.
Before the race you spoke about class.
-You have proved your class.
-Four.
You judged me the second time
without knowing me.
-You're doing it again.
- Three.
Two.
You have time until the race ends.
Go hard or go home.
One.
Oh, my God!
He's ripping his flesh apart.
First two contestants
They are dead meat, guys.
These dogs are really
going for it.
Number 10 is pulling the partner away
from the dogs.
Trust me.
It looks like more blood
than sweat.
That doesn't make sense.
Sid. Sid. Red flag.
I came here to dominate,
not to get eliminated.
Give a shout out
if you see the white one.
Look.
Okay, the Americans have chosen
safety with a red flag.
But remember,
the jackpot of this game is the white flag.
No!
After watching this,
I'll need a rabies injection.
Smart move by the Russian
saving her partner at the same time.
Run away, run away.
I didn't know anything
about your brother's death.
You knew that snitching to Dev
could endanger my life.
Whoa.
And the Israeli takes
himself to safety.
We did it.
And the Australian takes their
qualifying red flag.
And three more have qualified.
What a daring move by number 10.
Aka Crack.
Are you alright?
I am fine.
The flag. The flag.
-Quick. Let's go. Let's go.
-The flag.
There it is.
The Chinese, Arab and African
have obtained the flag
and made themselves safe.
Seven contestants have
qualified with the red flag,
and only the winning
white flag is left,
which will decide
this round's winner.
Ohh...one more death.
The flag has been kept,
in the middle of an electric fence.
And from here on,
as you just saw,
only the contestants can enter
the electric fence, not the dogs.
If he wins today,
he will be the crowd's favourite.
Siddhu! Siddhu!
There is only one option,
but it can kill,
both of us.
By doing this,
can I win your trust?
Can't say about trust,
but we can win the race.
Let's do this.
Here is the winner of race two.
Number 10, Siddharth Dixit.
-Yes. Yes. Yes.
-Hero.
Superman.
Yes. Yes.
Siddhu! Siddhu!
Happy birthday to you.
Happy birthday dear Dev.
Oh father.
We'll have a slightly different
type of conversation today.
And Maidaan's fate,
will be decided by playing.
Because my intentions will not change.
Your favourite vodka is in four of these glasses.
And one,
has death for you or me.
So before we start drinking,
we'll tell each other the truth.
Because we're both tired
of hearing lies.
I picked you up from the streets,
but never loved you like a father.
I always loved Maidaan more than you.
The biggest mistake of my life was,
that I thought you'll,
take Maidaan to new heights.
I was doing that.
After I am gone,
there are four others,
who will control the reins
of Maidaan.
The horse is long gone,
and you're still holding the reins.
No, no.
Don't worry.
I won't kill you.
After all, you're my father.
Zack.
Take him.
Dude, open the door.
Boss's orders.
No one is allowed outside.
Politicians don't know about you
taking over Maidaan.
Where is Mark?
Elise is taking good care of him.
Help me out.
What?
The founder Mark,
I want to meet him.
Why?
Only he can tell me
about my brother.
Hey, what did he say?
He said name of this place.
-Elise.
-Elise?
This is not just a piece of land.
It will be our world.
Freedom for Maidaan.
Only once the plutonium
has been delivered to them.
It will.
Hey, Sid. Come here.
I really want to,
but my focus is somewhere else.
Shut up.
Mark, the guy you're looking for,
is with some Elise.
And who is Elise?
My aunt.
I don't know.
Figure it out.
I got to go.
Can you do me another favour?
Sid wants you to look at this.
-Okay.
-Alright.
Listen.
The dude and the gal Elise
you're looking for,
all details are in the main server.
Will you take me there?
It's Ali Baba's cave.
It's your job to get in.
Do you like the Arab guy?
I love him.
Brother, I got you a date.
With the African?
Will you hit him for 25,000 dollars?
I will kill him for that much.
I really like him.
Strange. The fire is raging on both sides.
A fight. Just a fake fight.
Alright. Let's go.
Wow.
We have only 15 minutes.
Fifteen minutes only.
Elise. Mark. Nihal.
Find anything.
-Can't get in.
-Hey,
that's why you need an Indian.
Come on.
CCTV camera.
Cut the line from the main server.
I will kill you.
Follow me.
Wow. Nice.
All the files on Nihal
have been deleted.
But,
Elise's files are here.
Where does Elise stay?
Inside building, full network.
Inside lift, no network.
Metal blocks signal.
Ex-army, trust me.
Elise is not a person,
but a container.
Madam, weren't you suspended?
What are they doing with you?
They are here for the sake
of the country.
Awesome.
Even in my country Singham, Simmba
and Sooryavanshi come as a team.
Let's go.
The police got Mark out.
It was Patricia.
Get him back at any cost.
Alive or dead.
I've heard Dev's lie.
Now tell me your truth.
What did you do with my brother?
The final race that year,
was between Dev and Nihal.
He sabotaged Nihal's parachute's
release box.
I ignored this fact
even though I knew about it.
He was like a son.
Can I have your phone, please?
This is for you.
Hey, Dev.
Want to say something?
And look who else is here.
Our very own Nihal.
The champ.
Want to send a message back home, buddy?
Fun fact.
When I was a kid,
my mom used to say,
"Don't jump from trees."
Or you will get hurt.
Imagine if she sees me
jump from here,
she will faint.
And, father.
Don't worry.
Your son will return
after winning the race,
and show you the world.
And Siddhu, my love.
Brace yourself.
Next year,
your final race is against me.
Your older brother.
I showed your videos to everyone here.
They went crazy, Siddhu.
I told them
my brother is better than me.
They will invite you soon.
Okay, bro. Love you.
Take care.
So you work for him?
No.
I work for Dev.
Hey... no!
Stop. No.
And Zack,
works for me.
He always worked for me.
I will give you the location
and the password for the plutonium.
As promised.
Maidaan will always be about the game.
Nothing else.
I couldn't cherish a relationship.
But you must.
You are right.
You are a bad father,
and he's a bad son.
If I don't avenge Nihal's death,
I'll be a bad brother.
The subscriber you are calling
is currently not reachable.
Open fire.
01:43:00:18 0*1:43:02:06
...is currently switched off.
Got it.
Yeah.
Sir, Zack betrayed us.
The plutonium is gone.
And so is Mark.
No!
Maidaan! Maidaan! Maidaan! Maidaan!
Welcome.
Take on him.
Welcome to the final race day.
Today is a strange day.
A very strange day for Maidaan.
Such pain and betrayal,
Maidaan has never seen it before.
Hey.
Hey, what happened?
After all the hard work
and dedication,
can anyone abandon
their dreams?
But let's get to the point.
Actually,
seven contestants,
have given up.
I wish they had spoken to me once.
But it's sad.
Very...very sad.
Sid.
Open. Open.
But lucky for one.
So we do have a champ.
Contestant number 10.
Your favourite, Siddharth Dixit.
Siddhu! Siddhu! Siddhu! Siddhu!
Sid, are you okay?
Sid, what's wrong?
What?
This was your dream.
There.
I made it come true.
Even I had a dream.
But every dream comes with a price,
and every shattered dream
comes with a price too.
Which those seven players had to pay.
Why did you spare my life?
If I had killed everyone,
who would have grieved?
I didn't spare you.
You will die every day,
thinking,
why I sought those poor people's help.
Whatever happened, Sid,
is on you.
Anyway,
today is your day.
I made your victory easy.
Go, enjoy your dream.
The champ.
Siddhu! Siddhu! Siddhu! Siddhu!
I don't want your charity.
I don't want it.
Don't want it.
You came to watch the finals, didn't you?
And finals you will get.
I swear.
I am Siddharth Dixit,
number 10.
He says I am the champion.
So, Dev,
I challenge you
for the challenger race. Face me.
Come on.
I love it.
Of course, I accept.
But this time,
the race will have only one rule.
The winner,
gets to live.
Welcome to the challenger race.
This race starts from the top of the mountains
and continues in
a 700-year-old cave.
a jungle
and then after passing
through this city,
it will end at
its destination.
But this race is not against
each other
It will be played against time
A time bomb will be tied
on the arms of both players.
Which will blast twenty minutes
after the race starts.
The key to deactivate
this time bomb
will be obtained as soon as
the player puts the flag in the box.
Which is called,
the winning flag?
Three.
Two.
One.
Go!
Unbelievable.
Dev and Siddharth
have their eyes on the flag.
And we are witnessing
the clash of the titans.
And Dev has the flag.
-The champion showing his champion move.
-Unbelievable. Dev has done it.
At the end of the race,
this flag will get the key
that can save one man's life.
So both the players have to safeguard
this flag till the end of the race.
The bomb's tied on them,
but I am on the edge.
♪ Crakk. Crakk. Crakk. Crakk. Crakk. ♪
The winning flag
is with Siddharth Dixit now
Two players. Two cycles.
One flag
and one massive jungle.
And the race has moved
to the centre of the city.
And now Dev has snatched
the flag from Siddharth.
Let's go, Sid.
Get up.
Get up, Siddharth.
Get up, Siddhu.
Siddhu.
Go Sid.
Bro, tell me something.
How do you always win
the cycle race?
Duck, tuck, roll
Duck down.
Tuck your shoulders.
And look straight.
Understood.
♪ Move a little left,
move a little right.♪
♪ Watching my play,
everyone will be psyched. ♪
♪ Such is my nature,
madness knows no height. ♪
♪ My passion burns like fire,
be it day or night. ♪
♪ Never stop, never tire, like a carefree cloud.
Zipping through the skies all by myself. ♪
♪ I strike like thunder
out of nowhere. ♪
♪ Everyone accepts defeat
when they watch me play.♪
♪ There fun fight for another pay back.♪
♪ Win the phase and now gonna hold back.♪
The game has reached
its final stage.
Yes. Yes. Yes. Yes. Yes.
Come on.
Players have entered the arena.
What a crack move.
Come on. - Dev isn't giving Siddharth
any chance to grab the flag.
Looks like it's impossible
for number 10 now.
Poor number 10.
Looks like Dev
has made it again.
He's a two-time champion.
What will Siddharth Dixit
do now?
Number 10,
what are you going to do?
And...what a steal
to the finish?
♪ Crakk. Crakk. Crakk. Crakk. Crakk. ♪
Yeah.
The champion of the champion.
Siddharth Dixit.
Yeah.
Yes. Yes. Yes.
Siddhu! Siddhu! Siddhu! Siddhu!
Yeah.
The new champion of Maidaan.
Siddharth Dixit.
What the hell is happening?
-What is going on in Siddharth's mind?
-Why isn't Siddharth deactivating the bomb?
They don't call me crack for nothing.
I guess winning the race
isn't enough for number 10.
Looks like the boys want
another round at each other.
-Oh, my God!
-The boys are playing with their lives now.
Race is finished,
now it's your turn.
To get battered.
Your brother was found
in pieces.
No one will find you.
Only three minutes
for the bomb to explode.
Come on, Sid.
Only two minutes
for the bomb to explode.
Siddhu! Siddhu!
Oh, my God!
These boys are mad.
They are both crack.
Siddhu! Siddhu! Siddhu! Siddhu!
Siddharth.
Final forty seconds left
before the blast.
Siddhu! Siddhu! Siddhu! Siddhu!
A champion who uses
the race to kill people,
your Maidaan is over.
What the...
Siddhu! Siddhu! Siddhu! Siddhu!
Number 10,
Siddharth Dixit is the new champion.
Siddhu! Siddhu! Siddhu! Siddhu!
Hey, Siddhu.
♪ It's okay
if we couldn't be together for life. ♪
if I had to say goodbye. ♪
♪ It's okay
if you never hear about me again. ♪
♪ It's okay. ♪
♪ Always keep that smile on your face. ♪
♪ Take care. ♪
You fulfilled our dreams, Siddhu.
♪ For my sake, take care. ♪
Maidaan doesn't end here, it begins.
♪ Crakk. Crakk. Crakk. Crakk. Crakk. ♪
♪ One, two, three. ♪
♪ Move a little left,
move a little right." ♪
♪ Watching my play,
everyone will be psyched. ♪
♪ Such is my nature,
madness knows no height. ♪
♪ My passion burns like fire,
be it day or night. ♪
♪ Never stop, never tire,
like a carefree cloud. ♪
♪ Zipping through the skies
all by myself. ♪
♪ I strike like thunder
out of nowhere. ♪
♪ Everyone accepts defeat
when they watch me play."♪
♪ There fun fight for another pay back.♪
♪ Win the phase and now gonna hold back.♪
♪ I play fearlessly and daringly. ♪
♪ And my mind is a little... ♪
♪ Crakk. ♪
♪ Crakk. Crakk. Crakk. Crakk. Crakk. ♪
♪ Get out the way,
I am gonna. ♪
♪ Crakk. Crakk. Crakk. Crakk. Crakk. ♪
♪ Never stop, never tire,
like a carefree cloud. ♪
♪ Zipping through the skies
all by myself. ♪
♪ I strike like thunder
out of nowhere. ♪
♪ Everyone accepts defeat
when they watch me play."♪
♪ Crakk. Crakk. Crakk. Crakk. Crakk. ♪
♪ I play fearlessly and daringly. ♪
♪ And my mind is a little... ♪
♪ Crakk. Crakk. Crakk. Crakk. Crakk. ♪